<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pages>
  <page id="c8ffe9a587b126f152ed3d89a146b445">
    <title><![CDATA[About us]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[<h1><strong>ABOUT US</strong></h1>
<p>Extrema was among the first dance promoters and has been around since 1992. Besides organizing Solar Weekend in, among others, Oslo, Roermond and Ibiza, Extrema is also responsible for Extrema Outdoor in both Belgium (XO Belgium) and the Netherlands. This year marks the already 19<sup>th</sup> edition of dance festival Extrema Outdoor at recreational beach Aquabest.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong><br /> EXTREMA &hearts; PEOPLE &amp; PLANET<br /></strong>Since the early days Extrema has organized events simply to make people happy. We have taken that concept one step further and now, all of Extrema&rsquo;s events are being built on the foundation &lsquo;people &amp; planet&rsquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This entails Extrema's corporate social responsibility and the pursuit of this endeavor together with it's visitors, out of love for people and planet. For this reason, step by step, our events are being made more sustainable.</p>
<p>Among other projects, this is achieved by initiating, stimulating and organizing the following:</p>
<h1><strong>Planet</strong></h1>
<p><strong>TRANSPORTATION<br /></strong>By stimulating the use of carpooling and public transportation for both visitors and crew alike, we all do our part for a greener world. That is why we deploy coaches between Best train station and the festival grounds. For this we developed a special combiticket to go with your NS train ticket.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition, together with organizations like Event Travel we offer group travel bus arrangements from all over the country and it's neighbors, and the possibility for carpooling through Toogether..</p>
<p>For more information, <a href="../../../../../../nl/info#how-to-get-there%20" target="_blank">click here&gt;&gt;&gt;</a><br /><br /></p>
<p><strong>WASTE<br /></strong>To create more awareness, together with waste and environment concern Van Gansewinkel and the XO Trash Teams we make sure the festival grounds stay clean and the waste is sorted as much as possible, enabling easier recycling for the materials seperated!</p>
<h1><strong>People</strong></h1>
<p><strong>TAP WATER<br /></strong>Water belongs to everyone and is of vital importance! Therefore we think it is only natural to offer free drinking water at the various sanitation units located on the festival grounds.</p>
<p class="p4"><strong>SOUND</strong><br /> Of course sound systems are awesome and artists like to get the most out of them, but you have got to take care of your hearing. For this reason, already seven years ago Extrema was the first in Holland to cooperate with &lsquo;<a href="http://www.earproof.com/">Earproof&rsquo;</a> to make visitors aware of the damage loud music can do, in a positive way.</p>
<p>What's more, acurate sound reports by ditto measurements are made to assure noise pollution is being kept to a minimum for the neighbors.&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>ACCESSIBILITY FOR THE DISABLED<br /></strong>Anyone 18 or over is welcome at Extrema&rsquo;s events! We exclude no one. It is therefore important to us that people with, for example, a physical disability can experience the festival to it's fullest. That is why we make the festival grounds highly accessible by laying down driving plates and creating paved roads. Also sanitation for the disabled is found at every sanitation unit.</p>
<p>Naturally, we are open to ideas and evaluation pionts regarding this matter (and others!). We are always available through: <a href="mailto:info@extrema.nl">info@extrema.nl</a><a href="../../../../../../cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b6dfd8d0d9f6d3cec2c4d3dbd798d8da"><span class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="f990979f96b99c818d8b9c9498d79795"><br /></span>
<script type="text/javascript">// <![CDATA[
!function(){try{var t="currentScript"in document?document.currentScript:function(){for(var t=document.getElementsByTagName("script"),e=t.length;e--;)if(t[e].getAttribute("cf-hash"))return t[e]}();if(t&&t.previousSibling){var e,r,n,i,c=t.previousSibling,a=c.getAttribute("data-cfemail");if(a){for(e="",r=parseInt(a.substr(0,2),16),n=2;a.length-n;n+=2)i=parseInt(a.substr(n,2),16)^r,e+=String.fromCharCode(i);e=document.createTextNode(e),c.parentNode.replaceChild(e,c)}}}catch(u){}}();
// ]]]]><![CDATA[></script>
</a></p>
<p><strong>FOOD<br /></strong>We like good food, eating responsibly we like even better! That is why we offer several organic eating and drinking possibilities on the festival grounds, such as an organic French/Arabic caterer, the scrumptious tomato-lentil soup by Lizz Bizz, the sustainable and organic Wokmobiel which offers products from local farmers, and even ecological, organic fair-trade donuts! Bon appetit!</p>]]></body>
    <order>0</order>
    <language>en</language>
  </page>
  <page id="92cc227532d17e56e07902b254dfad10">
    <title><![CDATA[Q&A]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[<b>Timetable & Floorplan</b><br/><p>Are availlable in our festival app <a href="http://appmiral.com/app/extrema-nl" target="_blank">here &gt;&gt;&gt;</a></p><br/><br/><b>Is there an app?</b><br/><p>Yessurrr... You can find the iPhone and Android app <a href="http://appmiral.com/app/extrema-nl" target="_blank">here &gt;&gt;&gt;<br /><br /></a>There is also a special app for our opening and closing show<br /><a href="http://bit.ly/iPhoneShowapp2014" target="_blank">iPhone</a>&nbsp;-&nbsp;<a href="http://bit.ly/AndroidShowapp2014" target="_blank">Android</a></p><br/><br/><b>How about security and first aid on and around the festival premises?</b><br/><p><span>We have plenty of security personnel on and around the festival premises. Please be aware that these people are around for your safety and the safety of your loved ones, so please follow their instructions carefully. There will be a professional first aid station on site, clearly marked at the event.</span></p><br/><br/><b>What time does the festival start and end?</b><br/><p><span>The festival starts at 11:00 hrs and will end at 23.00 hrs.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Is there a minimum age?</b><br/><p><span>Yep, the minimum age to celebrate XO with us is 18. Be sure you have your ID ready at the entrance, folks!</span></p><br/><br/><b>Once I leave the festival premises, can I come back to the festival later on?</b><br/><p><span>Nope, once you decide to leave us, you won't be able to get back to the event.</span></p><br/><br/><b>What if I take medicins/have allergies?</b><br/><p>Do you need medicins during the festival? No prob, just make sure to bring all medical prescriptions. The accompanying names on the boxes should match the person&rsquo;s ID of course.</p>
<p>Do you want to bring your own food to the festival due to allergies?<br />That&rsquo;s no problem either. Just make sure you contact us a couple of weeks before the festival through mail at <a href=\"mailto:info@extrema.nl\">info@extrema.nl</a>, so we&rsquo;re able to inform you how to make the proper arrangements for this.</p><br/><br/><b>Will there be vegetarian and biological food served?</b><br/><p><span>Sure!</span></p><br/><br/><b>Will there be parking and toilet possibilities for disabled persons?</b><br/><p><span>Yes, there will be a disabled person parking as close to the entrance as possible. You are allowed to park there after showing your personal and official &ldquo;disabled person parking permit&rdquo;. Regarding the toilets; there is a special disabled person toilet in every toilet area at the festival premises. For questions please contact&nbsp;</span><a href=\"\\&quot;\\\\&quot;mailto:info@extrema.nl\\\\&quot;\\&quot;\">info@extrema.nl</a><span>.</span></p><br/><br/><b>I'm a breastfeeding mum. What about expressing breast milk?</b><br/><p><span>At the first aid area in the beach club we have a special area available for all this.</span></p><br/><br/><b>What about foto and video registrations?</b><br/><p><span>You are allowed to bring your camera when it&rsquo;s not a proffesional one. We like you to share your pictures with us on our Facebook page!</span><br /><br /><span>By entering this event you automatically agree and accept the terms of use of all video filming and photo image registrations and agree with Extrema and its media partners to use these images.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Are there Lockers at the festival?</b><br/><p><span>There are lockers available near the entrance of the festival.</span></p><br/><br/><b>What's not allowed</b><br/><ul>
<li>Violence and intimidating behavior, as well as discrimination and sexual intimidation.&nbsp;</li>
<li>Wearing any type of provocative clothing (like football shirts).&nbsp;No colours.&nbsp;</li>
<li>The possession of waepons, glass, spraycans, cans, fireworks and umbrellas.</li>
<li>The use as well as the possession of drugs. We have a &ldquo;zero tolerance&rdquo; policy regarding drugs.</li>
<li>It is not allowed to smoke indoors (in the tents), only outdoors.</li>
<li>It&rsquo;s fine to have a drink or two, but make sure you don&rsquo;t drink too much. Drunk visitors have to leave the festival.</li>
<li>Don&rsquo;t throw your waist on the floor. Please make sure you put it in the garbage bins.</li>
<li>Deliberately damaging or stealing Extrema&rsquo;s or other's property is prohibited.</li>
</ul>
<p>Visitors enter the festival ground at their own risk. The organization is not responsible for any kind of damage, both physically and mentally.</p><br/><br/><b>Lost & Found</b><br/><p>Did you loose some thing or found some thing?&nbsp;<br />Look it up on iLost via&nbsp;<a href="https://ilost.nl/org/extrema" target="_blank">this link &gt;&gt;&gt;</a></p><br/><br/>]]></body>
    <order>1</order>
    <language>en</language>
  </page>
  <page id="e2ef524fbf3d9fe611d5a8e90fefdc9c">
    <title><![CDATA[Disclaimer]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[<h1>General</h1>
<p>Extrema Outdoor eg, hereinafter referred to as XO, hereby grants you access to xofestival.nl (the Website) and invites you to buy what is offered. XO thereby reserves the right at any time to modify the contents or parts removed without notice to you about having to do.</p>
<h1>Limitation of Liability</h1>
<p>XO is committed to the content of the website as often as possible to update and / or supplement. Despite this care and attention it is possible that content is incomplete and / or incorrect.</p>
<p>Specifically for prices and other information products on the Website are subject to manifest programming and typing errors. Can be based on such errors do not claim agreement with XO.</p>
<p>The content of the Website is partially automated way obtained. XO does its best this content as often as possible to update and / or supplement. Nevertheless it is possible that the content is incomplete, outdated and / or incorrect.</p>
<p>Users can post content on the Website. XO this exerts no editorial control or supervision. XO will seriously investigate complaints about user content and intervene where appropriate. Please contact us via the contact form.</p>
<h1>Royalty</h1>
<p>All intellectual property rights concerning these materials lie in XO and its licensors and users. Copying, distribution and any other use of these materials is prohibited without written permission of XO, except and only to the extent otherwise provided in regulations of mandatory law (such as quotation right), unless otherwise indicated in specific materials.</p>
<h1>Other</h1>
<p>This disclaimer may change from time to time.</p>]]></body>
    <order>2</order>
    <language>en</language>
  </page>
  <page id="f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd">
    <title><![CDATA[How to get there]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[<b>Car</b><br/><p class="p1">Do you have space left in your car? Bring somebody! Offer your ride in the Toogethr carpoolapp and make your ride more fun, cheaper and much more sustainable. Sounds good? <a href="https://m.toogethr.com/group/extrema-outdoor" target="_blank">Click&nbsp;here &gt;</a><br /><br /></p>
<p>Address: Ekkersrijt 9004, 5692 KA Son</p>
<p><strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;">Arriving from the highway A58 Tilburg:</span></strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;"><br />Please follow the directions on the yellow signs.&nbsp;<br />Follow Nijmegen/Helmond and take exit number 6 called &ldquo;Ekkersrijt&rdquo;.&nbsp;<br />Go left at the roundabout. At the next traffic lights go straight ahead.&nbsp;<br />At the next traffic lights turn left. Please follow the signs Extrema and the instructions given to you by Extrema&rsquo;s certified personnel.</span></p>
<p><strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;">Arriving from Eindhoven (J.F. Kennedylaan) to Ekkersrijt:</span></strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;"><br />Please follow the directions on the yellow signs. Keep left and follow the highway A58&lsquo;s Hertogenbosch/Tilburg and take exit 6 &ldquo;Ekkersrijt&rdquo;.&nbsp;Go right at the roundabout. At the next traffic lights go straight ahead.&nbsp;<br />At the next traffic lights turn left. Please follow the signs Extrema and the instructions given to you by Extrema&rsquo;s certified personnel.</span></p>
<p><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;"><strong>Arriving from the highway A50 Son en Breugel/Oss/Nijmegen:</strong><br />Please follow the directions on the yellow signs. Keep right and follow Helmond/&nbsp; Eindhoven Centrum/ Ekkersrijt.&nbsp;<br />After about 600 meters still keep right and take exit 6 &ldquo;Ekkersrijt&rdquo;. Go right at the roundabout. At the next traffic lights go straight ahead. At the next traffic lights turn left. Please follow the signs Extrema and the instructions given to you by Extrema&rsquo;s certified personnel.</span></p>
<p><strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;">Arriving from the highway A2 Amsterdam/ &lsquo;s Hertogenbosch:</span></strong><span lang="\&quot;EN-US\&quot;"><br />Please follow the directions on the yellow signs. Do not take exit 28 &ldquo;Best&rdquo; of the A2. Follow the A58 towards Helmond/Nijmegen and take exit number 6 called &ldquo;Ekkersrijt.&rdquo; Go left at the roundabout. At the next traffic lights go straight ahead. At the next traffic lights turn left. Please follow the signs Extrema and the instructions given to you by our certified personel.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Parking</b><br/><p><span>With the XO+ parking ticket you can park your car near the entrance of the festival (soon available). Regular parking tickets are not available in pre-sale.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Public Transport</b><br/><p>Comin' by public transport? You can buy a special XO return ticket at&nbsp;https://www.ns.nl/eticket&nbsp;&nbsp;for train and bus. There will be special busses from Best train station to the festival and back. These busses wil start departing from 10:45AM till the end of the festival.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you travel only by bus from Best train station a return ticket will be 5 euro.&nbsp;<br /><br />The first bus will depart at 10:45AM and the last bus will leave from the festival till every body has left.</p>
<p class="p1">For the real party animals there is also a luxerious touringcar availibale, that has more than 140 departure locations in the Netherlands. Check it out at www.eventtravel.nl.&nbsp;</p>
<p><iframe style="border: none; padding: 0; margin: 0;" src="http://www.ns.nl/webwidgets/widget.jsp?width=360&amp;height=320&amp;data=eNpjqE3Os1VLTkpPtjU0Mzc3NzI0VSuH8AxMjA0sDNQyUOSSixJTbA1N1JLKbY3UkpJtDdTSwESx%0AraGRWlpmha2jWkqZbXCIf5haSiKYdkotLlFLKyu2TUvMKU5VSykGWldsGxSgauQc4AQA33Ik8A%3D%3D%0A&amp;ref=" frameborder="0" width="360" height="320"></iframe></p>
<h1>Going home by train after XO?</h1>
<h2>Check here the last trains departing from station Best.&nbsp;</h2>
<table style="width: 100%;" border="0" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td colspan="3" valign="top"><strong>Saturday Juli 13&nbsp;</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="3" valign="top"><strong><br /> Towards Eindhoven, Venlo/Roermond</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50"><strong>Tijd</strong></td>
<td valign="top" width="322"><strong>bestemming</strong></td>
<td valign="top" width="279"><strong>soort trein</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.30</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.22</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven, Weert, Roermond, Sittard, Maastricht</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.24</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven,Venlo</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.46</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.52</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven, Weert, Roermond, Sittard, Maastricht</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.00</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven, Helmond, Deurne</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.24</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven,Venlo</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.30</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.46</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">01.00</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">01.30</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Eindhoven</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td colspan="3" valign="top"><strong><br /> Towards Boxtel, 's Hertogenbosch/Tilburg</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50"><strong>Tijd</strong></td>
<td valign="top" width="322"><strong>bestemming</strong></td>
<td valign="top" width="279"><strong>soort trein</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.09</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Tilburg, Breda, Dordrecht, Rotterdam, Den Haag</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.09</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">s-Hertogenbosch, Utrecht, Amsterdam</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.28</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Boxtel, 's Hertogenbosch, Oss, Nijmegen</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.39</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Tilburg, Breda, Dordrecht, Rotterdam, Den Haag</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.39</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">s-Hertogenbosch, Utrecht, Amsterdam</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.42</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Boxtel, Tilburg, Tilburg Universiteit</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">23.58</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Boxtel, 's Hertogenbosch</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.27</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Boxtel, 's Hertogenbosch</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">sprinter</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.38</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">s Hertogenbosch, Utrecht</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td valign="top" width="50">00.39</td>
<td valign="top" width="322">Tilburg, Breda, Dordrecht, Rotterdam</td>
<td valign="top" width="279">Intercity</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><strong>&nbsp;</strong></p><br/><br/><b>Touringcars</b><br/><p><span>Follow the route to the A50 and take exit 6 to Industrieterrein Ekkersrijt. Follow the signs marked 'Touringcars' and the instructions by the traffic controllers.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Taxi</b><br/><p><span>The taxi stand for drop offs and pick ups is the Hallenweg. The taxi driver can follow the signs to the festival and from here you\'ll walk to the entrance in a couple of minutes.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Kiss & Ride</b><br/><p><span>For Kiss &amp; Ride go to 'Industrie terrein 't Zand'</span></p><br/><br/><b>Bike</b><br/><p><span>Bicycles and motorcycles have their own parking space. Take the bicycle route to Aquabest and follow the signs marked 'Fietsers' and the instructions by the traffic controllers.</span></p><br/><br/><b>Vervoer per luxe touringcar naar XO live?</b><br/><br/><br/><b>Transport by luxury coach to XO?</b><br/><p>Start your XO experience in one of our luxury coaches!&nbsp;From more than 152 locations in the Netherlands the coaches depart to XO.</p>
<p>Buy a combi ticket (entrance + bus trip) and save additional fee / handling costs or buy a single (two ways) bus trip! For all information check: <a href="http://www.eventtravel.nl" target="_blank">www.eventtravel.nl</a> or call +31(0)38-425 67 30.</p><br/><br/><b>Carpool</b><br/><p>Hot tip: carpool! Have you got a spot left in your car, or looking for someone to drive with you to and from XO Live. Just think of the benefits... Affordable, durable and probably very cozy! Yes, we LOVE carpooling. Find passengers or look for a ride <a href="https://m.toogethr.com/group/extrema-outdoor" target="_blank">here &gt;</a></p><br/><br/>]]></body>
    <order>2</order>
    <language>en</language>
  </page>
  <page id="bd4c9ab730f5513206b999ec0d90d1fb">
    <title><![CDATA[Hotels]]></title>
    <body><![CDATA[<b>4**** Inntel Hotels Art Eindhoven</b><br/><p>Address: Lichttoren 22, 5611 BJ, Eindhoven<br />&euro; 125.00 per person per night based on standard double room.<br />Single room rates upon request.<br />Credit card guarantee is obligated<br />For reservations + info call +31(0)40 - 751 3500 or <a href="mailto:reservations@arthoteleindhoven.com"><img src="../../../../../../images/hotel/reservation.jpg" alt="reserveren" width="100" height="20" /></a></p>
<p>This arrangement includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 overnight stay in design room, breakfast (until 11:00), entrance ticket (incl. ticket fee)&nbsp;</li>
<li>Shuttle bus to and from the XO &nbsp;terrain</li>
<li>Tourist tax</li>
<li>Late check-out until 13:00</li>
<li>Bookable at 12 July 2014 only</li>
<li>XO+ upgrade possible for &euro; 30,00 pp&nbsp;</li>
</ul><br/><br/><b>3*** NH Best</b><br/><p>Address: De Maas 2, 5684 PL, Best<br />Check in 12 July: &euro; 110,00 per person based on a standard double room<br />Check in 11 July: &euro; 139.50 per person based on a standard double room<br />Single room rates upon request;</p>
<h1><strong>SOLD OUT</strong></h1>
<p>This arrangement includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 overnight stay, breakfast (until 12:00), entrance ticket (incl. ticket fee)&nbsp;</li>
<li>Shuttle bus to and from the XO terrain</li>
<li>Tourist tax</li>
<li>Free use of swimming pool &amp; sauna</li>
<li>Late check-out until 14:00</li>
<li>XO+ upgrade possible for &euro; 30,00 pp&nbsp;</li>
</ul><br/><br/><b>4**** Holiday Inn Eindhoven</b><br/><p>Address: Veldmaarschalk Montgomerylaan 1, 5612 BA, Eindhoven<br />&euro; 125.00 per person per night based on standard double room<br />Single room surplus : &euro; 40,00<br />For reservations + info call: +31(0)40 - 235 8245 or <a href="mailto:reservations@eindhoven.holiday-inn.com"><img src="../../../../../../images/hotel/reservation.jpg" alt="reserveren" width="100" height="20" /></a>&nbsp;</p>
<p>This arrangement includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>1 overnight stay, breakfast (until 12:00), entrance ticket (incl. ticket fee)</li>
<li>Shuttle bus to and from the XO terrain</li>
<li>Tourist tax</li>
<li>Late check-out until 13:00</li>
<li>Bookable at 12 July 2014 only</li>
<li>Reservations can be changed or cancelled without costs until 1 July 2014.&nbsp;Afterwards the arrangement will be charged</li>
<li>XO+ upgrade possible for &euro; 30,00 pp</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p><br/><br/><b>Inntel Art Hotel Eindhoven</b><br/><br/><br/><b>For the artistic type</b><br/><h1><strong>Inntel Hotels Art Eindhoven</strong></h1>
<p>Sleep in style in the historical Philips Factory with its characteristic Light Tower. Each room comes with Italian designer bathrooms and, of course, a king size bed. Still not luxurious enough? We offer the the chance to upgrade to the special Art Jacuzzi room. Enjoy the bubbles and the view of Eindhoven&rsquo;s city centre.</p>
<p>1-, 2- or 3-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;129 pp<br />2-bedroom Art Jacuzzi + ticket starting at &euro;145 pp</p>
<p>Go to <a href="https://gc.synxis.com/rez.aspx?Hotel=61023&amp;Chain=10315&amp;locale=en-US&amp;arrive=7/11/2015&amp;depart=7/12/2015&amp;adult=2&amp;child=0&amp;promo=EXTREMA&amp;start=availresults" target="_blank">this page</a> for booking this package</p><br/><br/><b>For the easy type</b><br/><h1><strong>NH BEST</strong></h1>
<p>Groovy man. So close to the festival! And even a shuttle bus to bring and collect you. You&rsquo;ll save all your energy for Extrema Outdoor itself, &rsquo;cause dancing is inevitable. When waking up the next day, you&rsquo;ll be greeted with a lovely breakfast. Losing those last beads of sweat in the sauna is also included. Too hot for you? Wash away your hangover in the heated indoor pool. Checkout is at 05:00 PM.</p>
<p>1-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;165 pp<br />2-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;117,50 pp</p>
<p>Please contact&nbsp;<a href="mailto:nhbest@nh-hotels.com">nhbest@nh-hotels.com</a>&nbsp;for reservations.</p>
<p class="p1">&nbsp;</p><br/><br/><b>For the sporty type</b><br/><h1><strong>Holiday Inn</strong></h1>
<p>Hotel, motel&hellip; Nevermind. Swimming, sports, food but above all getting rid of your hangover. It&rsquo;s all possible at Holiday Inn Eindhoven. Enjoy a well-earned breakfast after a beautiful festival day and night. Sleep in with a late checkout at 13:00!</p>
<p>1-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;165 pp<br />2-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;125 pp</p>
<p>Please contact&nbsp;<span class="s2"><a href="mailto:reservations@eindhoven.holiday-inn.com">reservations@eindhoven.holiday-inn.com</a></span>&nbsp;for reservations.</p><br/><br/><b>For the sleepy type</b><br/><h1><strong>Blue Collar Hotel</strong></h1>
<p>Situated at hip Strijp-S and the Klokgebouw. The Blue Collar Hotel offers four different packages. What do they have in common? Free aspirin with a late breakfast, and checkout available at 14:00!&nbsp;</p>
<p>1-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;112,50 pp<br />2-bedroom + ticket starting at &euro;85,25 pp</p>
<p>Please follow<a href="http://www.bluecollarhotel.nl/en/events/extrema-outdoor-2015/" target="_blank"> this link</a><span class="s2">&nbsp;</span>for&nbsp;reservations.</p><br/><br/><b>For the traveling type</b><br/><p>Are you traveling from abroad? Find our special international packages <a href="../../../../../../en/info/packages">here &gt;</a></p><br/><br/>]]></body>
    <order>3</order>
    <language>en</language>
  </page>
</pages>
